The exciting balance adjustment is finally here! Just last night, Delta officially announced,
It is necessary to use the knife on the engineering parts with unbalanced strength. Update on July 10th,
Bit, nicknamed Taoist Priest Four Eyes, was first stabbed by the enemy. I don’t know Bit,
The official has made it clear that in the coming weeks, many excessive operators who have ruined the game experience will be corrected.
Bring the battle game back to a healthy and fair environment. Many players ridiculed,
The planner was afraid that he would be tortured terribly by the Bits who were squatting together in the blue game.
Let me first talk about how outrageous Bit was before. In the past, he would throw little spiders when he came up and would not fight you head-on.
If you are bitten by a small spider, the big spider will still follow you and catch you.
They can have countless opportunities to release the spider, but you can't make a mistake.
Even if you go to great lengths to kill these three college students,
But you find that their equipment is not enough for you to clear the spider's bullets. In this environment,
Those single and third anchors are also miserable. Don't don't! You said, I'm the one telling you,
Why am I asking you to chip away at these engineering bits? If there are no single or three anchors on Douyin platform who can withdraw,
Then his traffic will be poor.
So what does the traffic difference between single and three anchors mean? Your game traffic will also be poor. Remember,
To be fair, I am not egoistic. We want mutual benefit and symbiosis, right?
Look at this, how can I push forward? A W Bengfei is Bai Bengfei, look, look, look,
Look at this, look at this, those who mock me and say I'm a coward, please tell me who your favorite broadcaster is?
Can he kill three Spider-Men in a row in President?
After I download the show, I will learn how to wear three Spider-men in one role as CEO. O K,
I know how to play the single and three ranks. Encountered this.
Engineering people, the Three Engineering Triangular People, I don’t do that, I hate them until the very end!
I like engineering, um, and I like working in a district, hey! Fortunately, this change accurately targets the situation.
A new damage attenuation mechanism has been added to the Sentinel Brood. After sustaining corrosive damage from multiple small spiders in a short period of time,
Players will gain resistance, and subsequent spider explosion damage will be greatly reduced.
The change completely retains Bit's core gameplay of single-player exploration, but the three-person grouping is filled with spiders and relies on quantity.
The no-solution routine that directly kills the opponent is completely unworkable. For example, players don’t have to rush to break through defenses.
This nerf is just the beginning. Officials have sent out clear signals,
The three controversial operators Night Fight, Silver Wing, and Echo will be adjusted in batches in the next few weeks.
Especially the night battle planning was said to be easy to deal with.
I guess my thinking at the time was that the role had been in a vacuum for such a long time.
Compared to Bit and Old Man who have unlimited skills, their vacuum period is relatively long.
Threats should be controllable. As a result, although this character has a long vacuum period, you can't resist him because of his many skills.
With two ice crowns and a six-shot ultimate move, as long as your positioning is wrong and you freeze, you're basically done. In addition,
Information acquisition without blind spots in the entire Silver Wing map, large-scale interference and field control of echoes,
All have seriously squeezed the normal confrontation space. This time the official admitted it directly.
The skill strength of some operators has seriously exceeded the standard. Mitte is only a target for surgery in the first round.
In the subsequent night battles, the extremely strong large-scale field control and the overly transparent investigation information of Silver Wings will be adjusted.
No, this is definitely not a small tweak.
It is the official determination to rectify all underworld gameplay that destroys the balance of the game and discourages ordinary players.